James A. Davies

(859) 519-5855 J.Davies2099@gmail.com https://github.com/Jdavies00 https://linkedin.com/in/Jdavies00/

SUMMARY

Passionate Junior Developer with experience in networking, web development and customer service, prepared to leverage skills and experience to contribute to a team environment dedicated to growth and social responsibility. Dedicated learner with the ability to jump into projects and utilize critical thinking and troubleshooting experience to find solutions and pivot effectively and efficiently.

SKILLS

Coding

EDUCATION —

Awesome Inc. Web Development Boot Camp

Lexington, KY
Full Stack Development
Dec2020

Bluegrass Community and Technical College

Lexington, KY Associate of Applied Science in Network Technology May 2020

Bluegrass Community and Technical College

Lexington, KY
Associate of Applied Science in
Welding Technology
May 2020

EXPERIENCE

Waiter • Merrick Inn and Restaurant • Lexington, KY September 2019 - August 2020

- Provided excellent customer service to guests and team members
- Multitasked and problem solved during high volume slots

Low Voltage Electrician • Amteck • Lexington, KY August 2018 - January 2019

- Implement DHCP and DNS operations in a network
- Install and configure a firewall, proxy server, and network scanner
- Installed and terminated Cat6 and Fiber Optic cable
- Tested cabling to insure industry standards
- Installed hardware for physical security systems including accesscontrol Systems, Access Points, and PTZ Cameras

Waiter • Dudley's on Short • Lexington, KY October 2014 - September 2018

- Maintained impeccable customer service to ensure guest satisfaction and dining experience
- Received award for highest wine per-season sales
- Utilized organizational skills to manage business resources, including time and money